cantstopplaying.com 2017-12-10

# cantstopplaying | Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy”) describes how CantStopPlaying Inc (“CantStopPlaying” or “We”) collects and uses the information collected through the website at CantStopPlaying.com (the “Site”). This Privacy Policy is only applicable to the Site. This Privacy Policy does not apply to any other websites that you may be able to access from the Site, which may have data collection, storage, and use practices and policies that differ materially from this Privacy Policy.

We do not collect any personally-identifiable information. However, we use third party vendors (for example, Google) to cause advertising to appear on our Site. These third parties use cookies to serve ads based upon your prior use of our Site and other websites. You can opt out of the use of some of these cookies by visiting AboutAds.info. You may also be able to cause your browser to decline cookies. A user refusing cookies can still fully navigate our Site.

If you communicate with us by e-mail, we will use your email address to respond to you, and will then promptly remove your email address from our records.

We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy. Any such modification will be effective immediately upon posting on the Site. If any modification is unacceptable, your only recourse is not to use the Site.

If you are not yet 18, you are not allowed to use our services. Further, if we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from a child under age 13, please contact us

This website is owned and operated by CantStopPlaying Inc, PO Box 105603 #32118 Atlanta, GA 30348-5603.

You can contact us at: [cant.stopplaying@yahoo.com](mailto:cant.stopplaying@yahoo.com)

Effective Date: September 08, 2013
